serendeputy.com 2019-11-30

# Serendeputy Privacy Policy | Serendeputy: Newsfeed Engine for the open web

**I built Serendeputy from the ground up to be a useful tool for everyone, without all the stalking, surveillance and spam. Here are the details.**

This Privacy Policy describes how your personal information is collected, used, and shared when you visit or make a purchase from https://serendeputy.com (the “Site”).

### PERSONAL INFORMATION WE COLLECT

When you visit the Site, we automatically collect certain information about your device, including information about your web browser, IP address, time zone, and some of the cookies that are installed on your device. Additionally, as you browse the Site, we collect information about the individual web pages you view, what websites or search terms referred you to the Site, and information about how you interact with the Site. We refer to this automatically-collected information as “Device Information.”

We collect Device Information using the following technologies:

**“Cookies”** are data files that are placed on your device or computer and often include an anonymous unique identifier. These are what prevent you from having to sign in every time you come to the site. For more information about cookies, and how to disable cookies, visit [http://www.allaboutcookies.org](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/).

**“Log files”** track actions occurring on the Site, and collect data including your IP address, browser type, Internet service provider, referring/exit pages, and date/time stamps.

**Google Analytics**. We use Google Analytics to help us understand how our customers use the Site--you can read more about how Google uses your Personal Information here: [ https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/](https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/). You can also opt-out of Google Analytics here: <https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout>. 

**Twitter Information** : If you choose to connect your account with Twitter, Twitter will share with us your screen name, email address and a unique identifier. Beyond knowing that you've connected your Twitter account with Serendeputy, Twitter has no knowledge of what you do here. Connecting your account with Twitter gives us the ability to index the links coming through your home timeline. We cannot post on your behalf or interact with Twitter on your behalf in any other way.

When we talk about “Personal Information” in this Privacy Policy, we are talking both about Device Information and Twitter Information.

### HOW DO WE USE YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION?

We use your personal information, including the links coming through your Twitter feed and the interactions you make on the site -- bookmarking tags, clicking links, searching, etc. -- to provide you the newsfeed engine functionality.

### SHARING YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION

**We do not share your information with any third parties, nor use it outside the context of the Serendeputy application.**

That said, we may share your Personal Information to comply with applicable laws and regulations, to respond to a subpoena, search warrant or other lawful request for information we receive, or to otherwise protect our rights. 

### GDPR

If you are a European resident, you have the right to access personal information we hold about you and to ask that your personal information be corrected, updated, or deleted. If you would like to exercise this right, please contact us through the contact information below.

When you use the site, we will maintain your information for our records unless and until you ask us to delete this information.

### MINORS

The Site is not intended for individuals under the age of thirteen.

### CHANGES

We may update this privacy policy from time to time in order to reflect, for example, changes to our practices or for other operational, legal or regulatory reasons.

### CONTACT US

For more information about our privacy practices, if you have questions, or if you would like to make a complaint, please contact us by e-mail at jason@serendeputy.com or by mail using the details provided below:

Serendeputy   
60 Thoreau Street #302   
Concord, MA, 01742   
United States
